Good morning.
Hi. Thanks for letting me
- sleep here.
- Of course.
No, I didn't wake
you up this morning.
I figured maybe you
needed the rest.
Here's a coffee. And
I got some bread.
Anything on Pol?
So I went to the Meicho.
I spoke to the guy
who covers Yoshino
and all the little
towns in that area.
And they have not seen or heard
of any gaijin, any foreigners.
So I think we should file
a missing persons report.
- Mm. Yeah. Yeah.
- That's a great idea.
That is a fucking
brilliant plan.
You know, the Japanese
police department,
they love to waste
their whole fucking day
looking for a gaijin girl
who skipped out on her debts.
Is there any way that
Polina just went home?
No. She didn't go home.
Why? Are you sure?
I'm fucking sure.
Don't ask stupid
fucking questions.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- You want to smoke?
Listen,
Pol's my best friend,
but she's so openhearted.
She's very trusting. She
trusts people way too much.
She's so agreeable.
One night I was at Onyx, and
I was feeling really shitty,
and she came over to me
and ended up taking me
to her favorite
place in Tokyo and...
- The shrine?
- Yeah.
- See?
- That's what I'm talking about.
Where did you hear
about Yoshino?
The tip about Yoshino?
The host club that
she owes money to.
Okay. So we go back there.
We see what else we
can get out of them.
- No, no.
- Sato got it out of them.
And it turns out that
the club's in deep
with Sato's boss's, like,
mortal fucking enemy.
- Tozawa?
- Yeah. And Sato got spooked.
So he'll never go back there.
Wait. Okay. So this is great.
If Yoshino has anything to
do with Tozawa's operations,
I know a guy who knows
more about Tozawa's
operations than anybody.
- Okay. That's great.
- Let's talk to them.
Okay, the only thing is,
if we're gonna get
this guy to talk to us,
we're gonna have to go
to him with an offering.
Okay. Like what?
You have any idea where we
can score some crystal meth?
Improved Sync By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
Whoa, this is fucking cool.
Hey, who are you?
We met in a hostel in
Asakusa, right, Jake?
Yeah.
He saw I was
reading your article
on the Tozawa-gumi.
I'm obsessed.
And he said he knew the writer.
I thought he was
flirting with me,
but you know the fucking writer!
- She's cool, right?
- She's into this stuff too.
You ever gonna write about
Tozawa's plans in Tokyo?
- No, I write in my book, okay?
- Oh, yeah, the book.
He's writing a book
too. Isn't that cool?
- So cool.
- Yeah.
And, uh... we were
talking earlier.
We're really curious
about, uh, Yoshino.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yoshino?
It's like some deal that
Tozawa's got going on.
Sends girls who get
into debt there.
Hey, who you work for? Huh?
Um...
You're a newspaper man, right?
- No.
- How you know about Yoshino?
- Jake, Jake.
- I know it. I know it.
Give it to him.
- Take it easy.
- Give it to him.
Look, purest crystal
you're ever gonna get.
We know that Tozawa's got
something going on in Yoshino,
we think our friend is there.
Tell us what you
know about Yoshino,
and this is yours.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know about Yoshino.
Yeah, I'll tell you if you
party with me right now.
Little shabu, little
music, then I tell you.
Everybody happy, yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm not...
Yeah, sure. Fine. We'll do it.
No, no, no. I'm not...
I'm...
- Don't move.
- Okay.
Wait, what the
fuck are you doing?
I'm not... I'm not doing shabu.
What if I have a
heart attack and die?
- What's wrong with you?
- You have a condition?
- Yeah. I have a condition.
- I'm fucking scared.
I don't do hard drugs. I've
never done any hard drugs.
- Okay. Don't be scared.
- I've done this before.
I've done it with
the girls at Onyx.
I got this from them,
it's probably good.
We smoke, get what we came for,
and get the fuck out.
Come on, Jake, look at me.
Should have made a
better deal than that.
Trust me. Trust me.
Just go easy, okay?
Did I take too much?
What the fuck are you doing?
I said to take it easy.
Come. Dance.
Whoa.
- Good, right?
- Yeah.
My mix.
It's fucking great.
Okay, tell me about Yoshino.
We're gonna have a
good time, right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Fucking tell me.
Come on. Come on, man.
I'm smoked your meth.
Come on, tell me.
- Okay. I'll tell you.
- All right.
Tozawa Kumicho,
he make parties
there for friends
and business people
to have sex with models
and beautiful girls.
Get paid so much money.
Guest list, amazing.
Where in Yoshino? Where is it?
Where the fuck in Yoshino is it?
Come on, fucking tell me.
Where is it in Yoshino?
Address?
Yoshino is name of his ship.
It's a boat?
Where does it sail from?
The boat, where does
the boat sail from?
I don't know.
But if I get invitation,
maybe you come.
Yeah?
- Yeah. Okay.
- I look forward to...
Jake, it's time to go. Come on.
- No, no, it's not time, okay?
- Already?
Now is party time, all right?
Mm-mm.
Whoa, get the fuck off her.
- My hero.
- Yeah, what the...
Jake, let's go. Come on.
Holy shit.
Okay. Wrong way.
- Other way.
- Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go.
No fucking way. Polina
is not on a sex cruise.
She wouldn't let a client put
a hand on her fucking knee.
- I feel...
- Come on, come on.
- I feel good!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course you feel good.
You hit that pipe
like a fucking bong.
I feel like I can do anything.
- Stop.
- Okay, you need to calm down.
- No, I can't.
- I can't fucking do it!
- I just smoked meth.
- Jake, come on.
Jake, come on!
Okay. Okay, focus.
- Yeah.
- Come on, eyes here.
- Yoshino...
Yoshino.
It's not a place, it's a boat.
- It's a boat?
- It's a boat.
Tozawa uses it to get his
business associates laid.
It's fucking sick. It's
fucking hand out favors.
- Polina's on it?
- I don't know.
That is what we
have to find out.
We have to find out
where the boat is...
Nobody wants to
help me with this.
- And if she's on it.
- Nobody wants to fucking help me.
- Can you calm down?
- I fucked my sources up...
- Really, you gotta calm down.
- They don't trust me.
And by the way, I don't
really trust them.
I feel like everybody
is manipulating me.
Everyone's lying to me.
No one tells me the truth.
Come here.
Hey. Okay.
Okay.
You're a really
interesting person.
Oh, my God. It's my boss.
Oh, my God, I fucking...
Okay, wait, wait,
yeah. Okay. Yeah.
We're-we're gonna go back...
I'm gonna go back to work.
Okay.
And I'm gonna put
some feelers out
about the sex cruises.
- Here, take this in case you need it.
- Jake: And we are...
- Are you gonna be okay?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be good.
- You sure?
- We're gonna find her.
- Okay.
- Hey, Jake...
- We're gonna find her.
- Thank you.
- Call me, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay. Bye.
Oi! Oi!
Oi!
Speaking.
That is very welcome news.
Yes. Tonight.
I understand. Thank you.
Hey.
- Ho!
- We're going to the Meicho.
You want to come?
I'd love to, but I
gotta do something here.
And that's a great neck tie.
It's new. It's a new one, right?
Thank you. But it's not.
Where have you been?
Oh, I've been out
chasing a story.
Okay.
It's about this, uh,
this hostess I know
has a colleague,
a friend, another
hostess who went missing.
She racked up this
debt at a host club,
and she may have
been forced to go
on a secret Tozawa sex cruise.
That's her, this one.
What's the girl's name?
Her name is Polina. And...
How long has Polina
been missing?
Since Friday morning.
Her roommate was the
last one to see her.
I know the name of the
boat, the sex cruise.
I already know the name.
So I'm gonna make some calls
and see what I can find out.
Uh, are the phones
here safe to use,
or should I be using
my mobile phone?
Which one's better?
I'm not sure.
- What?
- Are you high right now?
- You're good.
- What did you do?
I did meth with a source
because it was the only way
I could get the information.
I'm not sure if you're
completely insane
or the most dedicated reporter
I've ever worked with.
- Jake...
- Yeah.
- Go before someone notices.
- Okay. Okay.
I'll fax the photo
to my contacts in
Missing Persons
and call you if
any hits come up.
Yeah, I'll make calls from home.
- Go.
- Okay, bye.
You're the best.
Samantha!
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Polina. They took her.
What? The guys from the boat?
- What boat?
- There's no fucking boat.
Men called and
say they took her.
They say she gave
them my number.
- Well, I want to... I want to...
- I want to fucking talk to them.
- Call them.
- I tried.
- Call them!
- I tried. It's unknown number.
- What do they want?
- We have to help her.
What do they want?
Everything she owes them.
10 million yen plus interest.
You fucking asshole.
- It's my fault.
- She was in debt because of me.
I know what you think, but
I have feelings for her.
But I don't have that much cash.
Please help me.
If they don't get it all today,
they say they're gonna kill her.
I'm serious, please.
- How much can you get?
- I don't know.
2... 2, 3 million
yen? How about you?
Call me in an hour.
Samantha!
Hurry up.
- They should be here.
- What are we looking for?
- The guy told me a blue van.
- You okay?
Yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
I'm about to hand over every yen
I have in the world.
If you fuck me over...
We both want her safe.
Blue van.
Give me your bag, I'll do it.
- What are you doing?
- Shut up.
You don't have her.
You don't have her. These
guys are so full of shit.
Ah!
Oh, shit.
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No!
Sorry!
No, no, no! No!
No, no!
This just seems too urgent.
- The money's been wired to me.
- I just can't access it yet.
You know, some technicality.
You know how these things are.
I just need a bridge
loan for a few days.
Miss, no legitimate
loan companies
will ever lend you money for
a business in mizu shobai.
Maeda-san, I have to
make the final payment
to purchase my club
now, or I lose it.
You have no assets,
no family, no collateral
if you cannot pay.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
- Duke.
- Hmm.
You are early,
for a change.
Can we talk?
I need a favor.
Hello, you've reached
the Adelsteins.
Neither Eddie, Willa,
Josh, nor Jessica
are here right now.
Please leave your
full name and number,
slowly and clearly, and
we'll get back to you.
Hey, it's me.
I just wanted to call and check
and see how everyone's doing.
- Josh.
- Hey, Dad?
I'm glad I couldn't sleep.
I've just been, uh,
catching up on some work.
It's good to hear your voice.
Yeah, sorry I haven't
been better about calling.
Uh, it's just been really busy.
I'm sure.
Well, take care of yourself.
Your mother worries.
How's Jessica?
Are you really asking,
or am I just supposed
to say everything's great?
- Can we not argue?
- Let's not argue.
Um, uh, yeah, I want to
know how she really is.
She's not good.
I know she tells you she's fine.
She needs you to believe
that, but it's, uh...
It's very bad again.
What if I came home?
Is that what you
really want, son?
Josh?
You sound tired.
Get some sleep.
When you wake up, if you
still want to come home,
I'll buy you the ticket myself.
Tomorrow.
Okay?
Hey. What are you doing here?
- Oi.
- Sato.
Hai.
If you came here to talk
me out of it, don't.
- It's too late for that.
- Oyabun wants to do business.
That's great news.
Samantha, you should know
who you are in business with.
I know the risk I'm taking.
I'm very aware of how fucking
wrong this could go for me.
Then why are you doing this?
Because I'm not
giving up my club.
I've worked too hard.
I've done too many things
to make this happen.
And it will make money.
What? Come on.
Nothing.
Any word about
your friend Polina?
I am sorry.
Truly.
The funds will be placed
in an account in your
name tomorrow afternoon.
I have been put in charge
of dealing with your club.
I hope that won't be a problem.
No. You?
No.
We will keep things
professional.
Absolutely.
New beginning.
I'd like that.
Me too.
- Good night.
- Night.
Hey, we have time, no?
We have plenty of time.
Come on, we have all
night. Yes, I know.
I thought you would
like that one.
Hey, come on. No, no, no.
Get off me. Get
off me. Get off me!
Don't fucking...
How dare you touch me like that?
Don't touch me like that.
Hey.
Are you crazy?
This... this mister attacked me.
This is not part
of our agreement.
Don't touch me. Don't touch...
Don't fucking touch me!
No, no, no! Don't!
Oi. Oi!
What happened to you?
Where's the family?
Out of town.
I've got something
you need to see.
Look, I know that I fucked up.
I know you don't trust me.
But I'm here asking
for a second chance.
Please.
Make sure you were not followed.